AMIR GAFNER

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

72 MAZE ST TEL AVIV 65789

(972) 58 400 33 46

☐ GAFNER.GITHUB.IO

in AMIR GAFNER

TIPSY-MECHANIC

JAVASCRIPT

EXPERT

NODE WEBPACK

REACT

REDUX

ANGULAR

BACKBONE

HTML5

CANVAS

D3, GOOGLE CHARTS

EXPRESS MONGO

EXTENSIONS

PYTHON, C++, PHP

EXPERIENCED

GOOGLE APP ENGINE BIG QUERY DOCKER COCOS2DX SYMFONY NGINX MYSQL

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH (FLUENT) HEBREW (NATIVE)

INTERESTS

Music, Art, Philosophy, International Relations, Mars

SUMMARY

Cutting edge front-end development experience in web-based systems, Front-end architecture to W3C-established web standards by maintaining cross-browser/cross-platform compatibility through validation, usability, interface design and user experiences. 8+ years of experience - JavaScript expert, advanced Node, Python.

EXPERIENCE

REACTFUL 2015 - 2017

FULL STACK LEAD DEVELOPER

 $Reactful\ helps\ convert\ visitors\ by\ creating\ powerful\ Reactions\ built\ on\ top\ of\ React/Redux,\ Node,\ Webpack,\ ES2017\ and\ isomorphic\ render$

- Developed and designed Reactful web application from the bottom up, designed, implemented, tested, ensured cross-browser and cross platform compatibility, Serving 800k unique sessions daily.
- Crafted user experiences, integrated design and system architecture. Implemented technologies including GCS, Stripe, Intercom and Segment
- Responsible for team repository, releases and feature roadmaps.

GUESTY INC. 2014 - 2015

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Airbnb management service built with Mean.js stack. Working in small agile team, building a real time dashboard/admin tool and backend

- Developing single page application for managing reservations, booking insights history, along with pricing analytics and listing stats.
- Integrating Stripe and Firebase for real time operation system.
- Managing more than 150k+ listings all over the globe.

SOMOTO LTD. 2013 - 2014

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Somoto Ltd. offers various solutions to software developers, publishers, advertisers, and Website owners for the distribution of software worldwide.

- Responsible for a reporting platform with data tables, graphs and charts serving 1000K+ users with 8M installs per day.
- Using Backbone and Marionette over NginX and Php Symfony framework.
- Building cross browser dynamically loaded extensions components used by 50M users bringing major impact on Mobile hands free Installs.

SIMPLIFIED NETWORKS INC.

2011 - 2013

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Moovu helps discover, collect and share videos from YouTube, Facebook, Vimeo.

- Developing Facebook connected Chrome extension for watching and collecting videos downloaded by 5M users
- Build a tool for creating a short meme gif youtube preview using canvas, creating gifs for viral video feed.
- Working in close collaboration within a cross-functional team to define and develop product roadmaps.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF HAIFA

2004 - 2008

BACHELOR MUSIC AND PHILOSOPHY

JOHN BRYCE SCHOOL

CERTIFICATE WEB DEVELOPMENT

1999 - 1999